<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<odoo>
  <data noupdate="0">
    <record id="ev_localization_homepage_service_head" model="ev_website.localization">
      <field name="name">service_head</field>
      <field name="en_value">Streamline Your Business with Expert Odoo Implementation and Customization </field>
      <field name="ar_value">تبسيط أعمالك من خلال تنفيذ وتخصيص Odoo باحترافية</field>
    </record>

    <record id="ev_localization_homepage_service_head_sub" model="ev_website.localization">
      <field name="name">service_head_sub</field>
      <field name="en_value">We help businesses leverage the full potential of Odoo by providing customized solutions, seamless implementation, and ongoing support - so your systems work the way you need them to. </field>
      <field name="ar_value">نساعد الشركات على الاستفادة الكاملة من Odoo من خلال تقديم حلول مخصصة، وتنفيذ سلس، ودعم مستمر – لتعمل أنظمتك بالطريقة التي تحتاجها.</field>
    </record>

    <record id="ev_localization_homepage_odoo_implementation_customization" model="ev_website.localization">
      <field name="name">odoo_implementation_customization</field>
      <field name="en_value">Odoo Implementation &amp; Customization </field>
      <field name="ar_value">تنفيذ وتخصيص Odoo</field>
    </record>

    <record id="ev_localization_homepage_odoo_implementation_customization_sub" model="ev_website.localization">
      <field name="name">odoo_implementation_customization_sub</field>
      <field name="en_value">We provide end-to-end Odoo implementation, configuring the system to meet your unique business needs. Whether you're just starting with Odoo or need advanced customizations, our team ensures a smooth setup with modules tailored to your operations. We develop bespoke solutions, automate your workflows, and integrate Odoo with third-party platforms for a seamless user experience. 
        With ongoing support and regular updates, we ensure your system remains optimized for your evolving business. </field>
      <field name="ar_value">نحن نوفر تنفيذًا كاملاً لنظام Odoo، ونقوم بتكوينه ليتناسب مع احتياجات عملك الفريدة. سواء كنت تبدأ للتو مع Odoo أو تحتاج إلى تخصيصات متقدمة، يضمن فريقنا إعدادًا سلسًا باستخدام وحدات مصممة خصيصًا لعملياتك. نقوم بتطوير حلول مخصصة، وأتمتة سير العمل الخاص بك، وتكامل Odoo مع منصات الطرف الثالث لتجربة مستخدم سلسة. مع الدعم المستمر والتحديثات المنتظمة، نضمن بقاء نظامك محسنًا لنمو عملك.</field>
    </record>

    <record id="ev_localization_homepage_reporting_analytics" model="ev_website.localization">
      <field name="name">reporting_analytics</field>
      <field name="en_value">Advanced Reporting &amp; Analytics</field>
      <field name="ar_value">تقارير وتحليلات متقدمة</field>
    </record>

    <record id="ev_localization_homepage_reporting_analytics_sub1" model="ev_website.localization">
      <field name="name">reporting_analytics_sub1</field>
      <field name="en_value">Our ERP solutions come with powerful reporting and analytics tools that provide you with real-time data insights. We offer customizable dashboards that track key performance indicators (KPIs), allowing you to monitor your business’s health at a glance. </field>
      <field name="ar_value">تتضمن حلول ERP الخاصة بنا أدوات تقارير وتحليلات قوية توفر لك رؤى بيانات فورية. نقدم لوحات تحكم قابلة للتخصيص لتتبع مؤشرات الأداء الرئيسية، مما يتيح لك مراقبة صحة عملك بنظرة واحدة.</field>
    </record>

    <record id="ev_localization_homepage_reporting_analytics_sub2" model="ev_website.localization">
      <field name="name">reporting_analytics_sub2</field>
      <field name="en_value">Our solutions also include in-depth reporting capabilities, enabling you to generate detailed financial, sales, and operations reports that empower data-driven decision-making.
      </field>
      <field name="ar_value">تتضمن حلولنا أيضًا إمكانيات تقارير متعمقة، مما يتيح لك إنشاء تقارير مالية وتقارير مبيعات وتقارير تشغيلية مفصلة تدعم اتخاذ القرار بناءً على البيانات.</field>
    </record>

    <record id="ev_localization_homepage_inventory_supply_chain" model="ev_website.localization">
      <field name="name">inventory_supply_chain</field>
      <field name="en_value">Inventory &amp; Supply Chain Management </field>
      <field name="ar_value">إدارة المخزون وسلسلة التوريد</field>
    </record>

    <record id="ev_localization_homepage_inventory_supply_chain1" model="ev_website.localization">
      <field name="name">inventory_supply_chain1</field>
      <field name="en_value">Our ERP systems include robust inventory and supply chain management features designed to streamline your operations. You can track your inventory in real-time, automate procurement processes, and gain complete visibility over your warehouse activities. </field>
      <field name="ar_value">تتضمن أنظمة ERP الخاصة بنا ميزات قوية لإدارة المخزون وسلسلة التوريد مصممة لتبسيط عملياتك. يمكنك تتبع المخزون في الوقت الفعلي، وأتمتة عمليات الشراء، والحصول على رؤية كاملة لأنشطة المستودع.</field>
    </record>

    <record id="ev_localization_homepage_inventory_supply_chain2" model="ev_website.localization">
      <field name="name">inventory_supply_chain2</field>
      <field name="en_value"> By optimizing your supply chain, we help you reduce costs, improve stock management, and increase overall efficiency. </field>
      <field name="ar_value">من خلال تحسين سلسلة التوريد الخاصة بك، نساعدك على تقليل التكاليف، وتحسين إدارة المخزون، وزيادة الكفاءة العامة.</field>
    </record>

    <record id="ev_localization_homepage_finance_accounting" model="ev_website.localization">
      <field name="name">finance_accounting</field>
      <field name="en_value">Finance &amp; Accounting </field>
      <field name="ar_value">المالية والمحاسبة</field>
    </record>

    <record id="ev_localization_homepage_finance_accounting_sub1" model="ev_website.localization">
      <field name="name">finance_accounting_sub1</field>
      <field name="en_value"> Our ERP systems simplify your financial operations by automating invoicing, billing, and expense management. You can easily generate financial reports, track budgets, and ensure compliance with tax regulations. 
      </field>
      <field name="ar_value">أنظمتنا ERP تبسط العمليات المالية من خلال أتمتة الفواتير، والفوترة، وإدارة النفقات. يمكنك بسهولة إنشاء تقارير مالية، وتتبع الميزانيات، وضمان الامتثال للوائح الضريبية.</field>
    </record>

    <record id="ev_localization_homepage_finance_accounting_sub2" model="ev_website.localization">
      <field name="name">finance_accounting_sub2</field>
      <field name="en_value">With our comprehensive finance and accounting features, you’ll have full control over your business's financial health, allowing for accurate and timely reporting.
      </field>
      <field name="ar_value">مع ميزاتنا الشاملة للمالية والمحاسبة، سيكون لديك تحكم كامل في الحالة المالية لعملك، مما يسمح بإعداد تقارير دقيقة وفي الوقت المناسب.</field>
    </record>

    <record id="ev_localization_homepage_crm_customer" model="ev_website.localization">
      <field name="name">crm_customer</field>
      <field name="en_value"> CRM &amp; Customer Engagement</field>
      <field name="ar_value">إدارة علاقات العملاء وتفاعلهم</field>
    </record>

    <record id="ev_localization_homepage_crm_customer_sub1" model="ev_website.localization">
      <field name="name">crm_customer_sub1</field>
      <field name="en_value">Our ERP solutions include powerful customer relationship management (CRM) tools that help you manage and nurture your customer relationships. Track leads and opportunities through every stage of the sales funnel, automate follow-ups, and improve communication with your customers.  </field>
      <field name="ar_value">تتضمن حلول ERP الخاصة بنا أدوات قوية لإدارة علاقات العملاء (CRM) تساعدك في إدارة علاقات العملاء وتنميتها. تتبع العملاء المتوقعين والفرص في كل مرحلة من مراحل مسار المبيعات، وأتمتة المتابعة، وتحسين التواصل مع عملائك.</field>
    </record>

    <record id="ev_localization_homepage_crm_customer_sub2" model="ev_website.localization">
      <field name="name">crm_customer_sub2</field>
      <field name="en_value">Our CRM system ensures that no opportunity slips through the cracks, boosting customer engagement and satisfaction.
      </field>
      <field name="ar_value">يضمن نظام CRM الخاص بنا عدم تفويت أي فرصة، مما يعزز تفاعل العملاء ورضاهم.</field>
    </record>

    <record id="ev_localization_homepage_sales_commerce" model="ev_website.localization">
      <field name="name">sales_commerce</field>
      <field name="en_value">Sales &amp; E-commerce Integration</field>
      <field name="ar_value">البيع وتكامل التجارة الإلكترونية</field>
    </record>

    <record id="ev_localization_homepage_sales_commerce_sub1" model="ev_website.localization">
      <field name="name">sales_commerce_sub1</field>
      <field name="en_value">Our ERP systems provide a seamless integration of sales and purchase processes. From managing sales orders and automating purchase orders to integrating your e-commerce platform, we ensure that every part of your business operates smoothly.
      </field>
      <field name="ar_value">توفر أنظمة ERP الخاصة بنا تكاملاً سلسًا بين عمليات البيع والشراء. من إدارة أوامر البيع وأتمتة أوامر الشراء إلى تكامل منصة التجارة الإلكترونية الخاصة بك، نضمن أن يعمل كل جزء من عملك بسلاسة.</field>
    </record>

    <record id="ev_localization_homepage_sales_commerce_sub2" model="ev_website.localization">
      <field name="name">sales_commerce_sub2</field>
      <field name="en_value">This integration leads to faster order processing, better inventory management, and a more cohesive customer experience across all sales channels.
      </field>
      <field name="ar_value">يؤدي هذا التكامل إلى تسريع معالجة الطلبات، وتحسين إدارة المخزون، وتجربة عملاء أكثر تماسكًا عبر جميع قنوات البيع.</field>
    </record>
  </data>
</odoo>
